lensbaby.com 2018-11-27

# Privacy Policy | Creative Effect Camera Lenses | Lensbaby

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Lensbaby, Inc. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the lensbaby.com website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Lensbaby, Inc.

Personal identification information: We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Non-personal identification information: We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. Web browser cookies Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

How we use collected information: Lensbaby, Inc. may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

– To improve customer service: Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
– To personalize user experience: We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
– To improve our Site: We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
– To process payments: We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.  
– To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature  
– To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.  
– To send periodic emails: We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How we protect your information:

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.

Sharing your personal information:

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information, not linked to any personal identification information  _without the User’s express consent,  _regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

Third party websites:

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies.  We use one or more companies to place advertisements for our products and services and those of third parties on our Site and third-party sites. Cookies and other technologies such as Web beacons or tags are used to measure the effectiveness of our ads and to determine the display of content and advertising to you based on your interests both on our site, as well as on third-party sites and mobile apps where you may visit. To support this interest based advertising solution, we, and companies who we have contracted with, may use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to our and other Web sites. The information collected does not enable any third-party to identify you individually, without appropriate notice or consent. Although it is our hope that you find the display of advertising to you based on your non-personally identifying browsing interests valuable, if you would prefer not to participate in the services offered through these solutions, you can always opt-out of this activity by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) website by clicking http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp, or http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2#!/, or, if you are in the EU, by visiting: http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

Third Party Partner | Data Feature Used / Data Shared  
---|---  
Google Analytics | Remarketing Audiences  
Interests and Demographics Report  
Transaction Data  
Google AdWords | Remarketing Audiences  
Custom Audiences  
Transaction Data  
Google Optimize | A/B Test Targeting  
Transaction Data  
YouTube | Remarketing Audiences  
Transaction Data  
Facebook & Instagram | Remarketing Audiences  
Custom & Lookalike Audiences  
Product Interaction Data  
Transaction Data  
WooCommerce | Ecommerce Platform  
Mailgun | Shipping & Confirmation Emails  
via WooCommerce  
Webgility | WooCommerce, Quickbooks and  
Shipping Label Connector  
Stripe | Payment Processing  
OwnerIQ | Digital Display Advertising  
Disqus | Commenting and Product Reviews  
LuckyOrange | Dynamic Heatmaps  
Chat  
Visitor Recordings  
Conversion Funnels  
Polls  
Form Analytics  
  
Changes to this privacy policy Lensbaby, Inc. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. Your acceptance of these terms By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. Contacting us If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: Lensbaby, Inc. lensbaby.com 824 SE 16th Avenue Portland, OR 97214 USA 971-223-5662 customerhappiness@lensbaby.com This document was last updated on May 24, 2018.
